question_data = [
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Film",
     "question": "In the movie 'Spider-Man: No Way Home,' all three live-action Spider-Man actors appear together.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},

    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Film",
     "question": "The movie 'Dune' (2021) is directed by Christopher Nolan.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},

    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Film",
     "question": "'Everything Everywhere All At Once' won the Academy Award for Best Picture in 2023.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},

    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Film",
     "question": "The film 'Avatar: The Way of Water' is the sequel to James Cameron's 'Avatar' from 2009.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},

    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Film",
     "question": "The character Barbie was portrayed by Margot Robbie in the 2023 movie 'Barbie.'",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},

    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Film",
     "question": "In 'Oppenheimer' (2023), Cillian Murphy plays the role of Albert Einstein.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},

    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Film",
     "question": "The movie 'The Super Mario Bros. Movie' features Chris Pratt as the voice of Mario.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},

    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Film",
     "question": "The horror film 'Smile' was released in 2023.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},

    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Film",
     "question": "'Black Panther: Wakanda Forever' marked the first appearance of the character Namor in the Marvel Cinematic Universe.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},

    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Film",
     "question": "Tom Cruise performed all of his stunts in 'Mission: Impossible - Dead Reckoning Part One.'",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
]
